let questions = [
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: '',
        options: [
            '',
            '',
            '',
            ''
        ],
        answer: 10
    }
]